[Music] Having
[Música]
said that, come on, I was also telling you
dicho esto venga e también me comentaba
that there's been a problem, I haven't seen you
que ha habido problemática no he visto
around here, I don't know who the [ __ ] I was saying, let's
por aquí no sé quién [__] decía a ver
see, excuse me, eh Let's see who it was. Ah Samuel
perdón eh A ver quién ha sido Ah Samuel
Díaz, Samuel Díaz, you know you smell like me,
Díaz que Samuel Díaz sabes que me hueles
man. With all due respect, eh Samuel, you
tío Con todo el respeto eh Samuel me
smell like the typical guy, the typical guy who knows how to
hueles al típico al típico tío que se la
Turbo operate cryptocurrencies. You
Turbo operan las criptomonedas que has
came here just to see if there's gossip, looking to
venido solo a ver si hay salseo buscando
throw the headline at me, I'm not eating because
aquí tirarme el titular no como porque
your name doesn't ring a bell. So I'm not going, no, I'm not
no me suena tu nombre Entonces no voy no
going with malice, okay. I don't want you to
no voy con maldad vale No quiero que
think that I don't like you or anything.
pienses que me caes mal ni nada
Just no, I don't know your name, and
Simplemente no no me suena tu nombre y
of course, when I see a guy named Samuel Díaz,
claro cuando veo a un tal Samuel Díaz
who I've never seen write in my
que no no lo he visto escribir en mi
life, Samuel, you're here, let's see how he [ __ ] your
vida Samuel estás aquí a ver cómo te fó
dick like Ed, I'm laughing my balls off.
la [__] como Ed me parto los [__]
Samuel is here, like Ed, I'm laughing my
está aquí Samuel como Ed me parto los
balls off, he tells me, hey, my delox. What's
[__] que me dice oye mi delox Qué
up with cript bru versus Javi Oliveira
onda con cript bru versus Javi oliveira
these last few days? I'm going to crypt bru and I'm
los últimos días Le voy a crypt bru y le
going to crypto bru, damn, but what's Caro's doing,
voy a crypto bru [__] pero qu de Caro
but it's someone from here that's definitely going to
pero es Es alguien de aquí fijo para
make the headline and for me to be
sacar el titular y que yo ahora esté
seeing this now, eh. I'm going to  to Cristo bru But
viendo esto eh Le voy a Cristo bru Pero
who's going to go to Cristo bru yes yes to
quién le va a ir a Cristo bru si si a
Cristo bru not even himself is going to go now
Cristo bru no se va ni él mismo ahora
let's see if the note has left eh
vamos a verlo si se ha pirado el nota eh
yes looked at the note says that he is not going to
si mirado el nota dice que ya no va a
comment anymore gossip But he has said that
comentar más salseo Pero eso lo ha dicho
25 times tomorrow he will appear here
ya 25 veces mañana aparecerá por aquí
again looking for attention I'm going to crypt
otra vez buscando casito le voy a crpto
bru to see as if it were this the red the
bru a ver como si fuera esto el rojo el
black and it seems like you write to me in in
negro y parece como que me escribes en
in Andalusian no because crypt bru instead
en en andaluz no porque crypt bru en vez
of crypt bru crypt bru no Honestly
de crypt bru crypt bru no Honestamente
I don't give a damn I mean no I don't give a damn
me la pela O sea no no me la puede pelar
anymore I mean That's my Flow right now Clear clear
más O sea Ese es mi Flow ahora mismo
what happens is that it would be
Claro claro lo que pasa es que estaría
good delox that eh I don't know if it's going to be
bien delox que eh No sé si va a ser
mentioned eh Maybe I'll go ahead and it's going to bec
menci eh A lo mejor me adelanto y va a
mention the other day Cristo bru got
serc mención el otro día Cristo bru se
really angry that by the way the video
picó muchísimo que por cierto el vídeo
that Cristo bru made the video that he made for me
que hizo Cristo bru el vídeo que me hizo
man instead of watching the original we saw it
tío en vez de ver lo original lo vimos
in the summary that outer Play made and I
en el resumen que hizo outer Play y lo
should have watched it in the original man
tenía que haber visto en el original tío
because then I put it on at night I don't
porque luego me lo puse por la noche no
remember why I think it was
me acuerdo el Por qué creo que fue
because  it happened I don't think it was because
porque me lo pasó No creo que fue porque
someone quoted it on Twitter that on
alguien lo citó en Twitter que en
Twitter the guy has it uploaded too,
Twitter lo tiene subido también el
trying by all
colega intentando por todos los medos
possible means to get it seen by as many people as possible, you
posibles que lo vea la más gente posible
know and the guy Oh Elena Thank you so much,
sabes y el tipo Oh Elena Muchísimas
the best way to lose a few
gracias lo mejor para perder algunos
kilos for obesity is to get rid of the
kilos para la obesidad es quitarte lo
most peripheral things you can
más Periférico de lo que puedes
easily do without and keep it off
prescindir fácilmente e irlo manteniendo
and reward yourself by seeing how the kilos fall off
y recompensarte viendo con cae los kilos
And go out for walks and flirt
Y salir a pasear y a ligar Muchas
Thank you so much Elena for that great
gracias Elena por ese pedazo de Super
chat, the thing is I don't understand
chat lo que pasa es que no entiendo
getting rid of the most peripheral things I don't understand
quitarte lo más periférico no entiendo a
what you mean by that with peripheral
qué te refieres con eso con periférico
a kiss eh thank you so much really I mean
un beso eh muchísimas gracias de verdad
this is the Christ man that's what I
O sea este el Cristo tío eso lo que os
was telling you the [ __ ] video that made me
iba diciendo el [__] vídeo que me hizo
laugh I mean I'm not going to
un descojone O sea ya no lo voy a
react to it because it's like too late
reaccionar porque ya es como muy tarde
no To watch that but a laugh a laugh
no Para ver eso pero un descojone un
a [ __ ] [ __ ] what the [ __ ]
descojone un des [__] qué el [__]
video the guy saying oh I saw it I
vídeo el tío diciendo ay que lo vi me
was laughing my ass off man man but no I have
estuve descojonando tío tío pero no Yo
n't seen this man and then I don't know what
no he visto esto tío y luego no sé que
we were commenting on the next day
estábamos comentando al día siguiente
also no And it was when  appeared in the
también no Y fue cuando apareció por el
chat your wife told me I don't know what
chat me puso tu mujer no sé qué me
blocked me do you remember we were here
bloqueó os acordáis estábamos aquí en
live she blocked me and And the guy uploaded this I
directo me me bloqueó y Y subió esto el
mean your wife is cheating on her your children the
tío o sea tu mujer la engaña tus hij los
Andalusians don't speak Spanish says delox
andaluces no hablan español dice delox
maybe for treating your Latinos badly By the
vez por tratar mal a tus latinos Por
way nimbus called him a scammer what do you
cierto nimbus lo llamae estafadora a qu
notice yes things like that no like I had
notas sí cosas así no como que yo había
called delox a scammer eh By nimbu and it's
llamado estafadora delox eh Por nimbu y
as if I haven't called delo a
es como si yo a delo no lo he llamado
scammer you called him until you
estafador lo llamabas tú hasta que te
started taking pictures with him because you
empezaste a hacer fotos con él porque
saw that the pambi topic was viral
que viste que era viral el tema de pambi
And then you wanted to put it in with a
Y entonces te quisiste meter con
shoehorn Look for fame you know but trust yourself
calzador Busca fama sabes pero fíate tú
the and the comment of a 5 year old boy no you
el e el comentario de niño de 5 años no
cheat on your wife just like your
a tu mujer la engañas igual que a tu
audience
audiencia
@javier perrito and what does he tell your little girls I
@javier perrito y a tus hijitas qué les
mean it's like the typical
cuenta o sea es como el típico
comment that a little boy makes
comentario e que hace un niño pequeño
to try to hurt you I mean this no he
para intentar herirte o sea esto no no
's not saying anything that will hurt you
está diciendo ni algo que te haga daño
not of your life because imagine what he
no de tu vida porque imagínate que te
says to you Imagine that my father has died
dice Imagínate que mi padre se ha muerto
and he says your father  I would be ashamed of you it's not
y dice tu padre se avergonzaría de ti no
a comment in which they are
es un comentario en el que están
putting the iriente family you know but
metiendo la familia iriente sabes pero
here they are pressuring for for for to
aquí es que están presionando por por
see if it hurts me no And how does it blow
por a ver si me duele no Y como la sopla
dude I mean Look there's a picture of you that was
tío o sea Mira hay una foto tuya que era
at an event in Madrid dude that they
en un evento de Madrid tío que la
put it up the other day and the [ __ ] picture
pusieron el otro día y la puñetera foto
smells dude I mean eh if I see you in person
huele tío o sea eh si te veo en persona
Christ bru m I'll probably come over to say
Cristo bru m Seguramente me acerca a
good morning to you and you pee up
darte los buenos día y te meas en lo
high and nobody's going to notice that you
alto y nadie se va a dar cuenta que te
peed up high because the smell is going to
has meado en lo alto porque el olor va a
be the same you understand me I mean I don't know if
ser el mismo me entiendes o sea no sé si
you have the picture handy Lili but
tenéis la foto a mano Lili pero es que
the [ __ ] picture smells dude I mean the
la puñetera foto huele tío O sea la
[ __ ] picture smells and what do you
puñetera foto huele y que a mí que tú te
get into with me and put and your little girls if
metas conmigo y pongas y tus hijitas si
I don't have little girls [ __ ] I don't have little
yo no tengo hijitas [__] yo no
girls you idiot that you don't
tengo hijas tonto que no no te enteras
even know where you're standing dude
ni ni de dónde estás de pie tío
give back to your followers the money
devuélvele a tus seguidores el dinero
that you made them lose okay while
que le hiciste perder vale mientras que
you were getting rich with that [ __ ]
tú te hacías rico con la [__] [__] esa
copy trading [ __ ] that you  you invented
de copy trading que que te inventaste
okay you're a coward don't you dare meet
vale que eres un cobarde no te atreves a
me in court okay
verte conmigo en un juzgado vale nada
just insult like a rat a
más que insultas como una ratilla un
little kid there a rat kid Okay
niño pequeñito ahí un niño rata Vale
well dude you've come off as a
pues muy bien tío has quedado como un
[ __ ] coward that's it without further ado V to me that I piss myself well I stand
[__] cobarde ya está sin más V a mí que
pathetic where are they
meo pues me pare patético dónde están
where are the notes saying coming out
dónde están los notas diciendo saliendo
to say this no delo no Oh if they get
a decir esto no el delo no Ay si se
involved with spirit if they mess with Willy re
meten con nimo si se meten con Willy re
damn delo tell the truth what do you think of
[__] delo di la verdad qué opinas de
these tweets don't you feel ashamed of these tweets
estos twit no te da pena estos twit
delox and all these channels that
delox y todos los canales estos que
defended this guy we don't feel ashamed of
defendían a este tipo no nos da pena
these tweets not one has come out to
esto estos twit ni uno han salido a
say anything not one has come out to say
decir nada ni uno han salido a decir
anything about these tweets these are pathetic I mean
nada de estos twit estos dan pena o sea
they're an attempt to be hurtful but [ __ ]
son un intento de hiriente pero [__]
embarrassing dude [ __ ] embarrassing Do you think that
pena tío [__] pena Tú te crees que a mí
at this point This is going to
a esta altura Esto me va a hacer
tickle me Senda I love you I love you
cosquilla Senda te quiero te quiero
Senda Thank you very much for that super chat
Senda Muchas gracias por ese super chat
says Leo González Javi Dallas also
dice Leo González Javi Dallas también
does copy trading and many lost Leo
hace copy trading y muchos perdieron leo
but Dallas [ __ ] your mother you're
pero Dallas se [__] a tu madre estás
all [ __ ]  day putting [ __ ] those
todo el [__] día poniendo gilipo eses
there man look look Christ bru You think
ahí tío mira mira Cristo bru Tú crees
that you put that tweet to me and you in my
que tú me pones ese tweet y tú en mi
face you're going to tell me the same thing or in the
cara me vas a decir lo mismo o en el
same tone if it was who called and almost
mismo tono si fue a quien llamada y casi
meme you on call On discord that I can't tell
te memea en llamada Por discord que no
you anything and almost meme you this
te puedo cen nada y casi te memea esto
what the [ __ ] is this what the [ __ ] is with the
qué [__] es esto qué [__] es con el
money that he has taken from people with
dinero que le ha sacado a la gente con
copy trading he didn't give you enough to buy the
el copy trading no te dio para comprarte
complete outfit and buy some
el el conjunto completo y comprarte unos
shoes Also apart from the
zapatos También aparte del uniforme del
school uniform this what the [ __ ] is it true those who mess
cole esto qué [__] es de verdad los que
with me man it's really fabric eh it's that wow it's that they
se meten conmigo tío es que vaya tela eh
are all the same man
es que vaya es que son todos iguales tío
my flowes I have more important things
mi flowes yo tengo cosas más importantes
than if one has fought with another another
que si uno se ha peleado con otro otro
with one friends you know like no that's not going to
con uno amigos sabes en plan no eso no
change the pre if it seems like it seems like
va a cambiar el pre si parece si parece
a lesbian what the [ __ ] am I really
una lesiana qué [__] es yo yo de verdad
those who mess with me are all the
los que se meten conmigo son todo
same bitcoin dude Well if they have
iguales tío de bitcoin Pues si se han
fought that what do I know how to
peleado que que se
do this of the lawsuits and Aha eh
a hacer esto de las demandas e Aha eh
[ __ ] Look at some the two lawsuits that I
[__] Mira unas las dos demandas que
filed last year man have now
puse el año pasado tío ahora le han
arrived eh to the  two people who are from
llegado eh a las dos personas que son de
telesalseo of La Movida de telesalseo I'm not
telesalseo de La Movida de telesalseo no
going to tell you But what a [ __ ] laziness how
os voy a contar Pero qué [__] pereza lo
slow that goes I mean tell me to me by
lento que va eso o sea dime tú a mí para
the time the trial is resolved they will
cuando se solucione el juicio sí que van
read the verdict and maybe they will
a leer el fallo y a lo mejor me van a
pay me something good but the only one that I'm
pagar algo bueno pero la única que se
going to keep well the ones that are
voy a mantener bueno las que están
there obviously I can't remove they ca
puestas evidentemente no la puedo quitar
n't be removed unless
no se pueden quitar a no ser que se
you reach an agreement or something
llegue sabes a un acuerdo o algo por el
like that that doesn't look good but the one that I'm
estilo que no tiene pinta pero la que sí
going to keep and maybe I'll put a
voy a mantener y a lo mejor pongo una
second one is the laserlent T I mean that
segunda es al laserlent T O sea ese
kid I don't know if he's obtuse
chaval yo no sé si es que es obtuso así
like Tania or some special little creature
como la Tania o una criaturita así
but they still get CP to
especial pero me llegan CP todavía a día
this day man that now there are no gossips from
de hoy tío que ahora no hay ni salseos
me or gossips from Dallas since
míos ni salseos del Dallas ya que el
Dallas Not even the gossip channels are
Dallas Ya ni los canales de salseo están
trying and yes the guy with his movie
tratando y sí que el tío con su película
his accusations of pedophilia those
sus acusaciones de de pedofilia esas
things his his putting me in also with some
cosas su su meterme a mí además con unos
terms man it's like there's no solution and
términos tío es como no tiene solución y
that guy hasn't received the first
ese no le ha llegado todavía la primera
lawsuit yet man I asked the
demanda tío que le pregunté a la
attorney gave What's up you know and why has
procuradora dio Qué pasa sabes y por ha
the sec been on sick leave from I don't know what from
estado de baja la sec de no sé qué del
his court I don't know a move okay
juzgado suyo no sé una movida vale no le
the first lawsuit hasn't arrived But
ha llegado a la primera demanda Pero a
maybe I'll file the second one on him
ese a lo mejor sí le pongo la segunda
without any kind of pressure because he's going to keep
sin ningún tipo de pris tal pues se va a
quiet for life You know without any kind of
callar la vida Sabes sin ningún tipo de
rush and let it be a mortgage That he
prisa y que sea una hipoteca Que él se
starts lying with me okay for his
vaya echando conmigo vale para su vida
whole life okay but I've
entera vale pero yo ya por temas de esto
been talking to a friend about this like this I was
así de de tal estve hablando tod con un
almost talking to him in
colega casi que prefiero responderle en
a video I tell him four things I put it
un vídeo le digo cuatro cosas lo pongo
somewhere You know why he can't see he's really
en un sitio Sabes porque es que no ve es
slow man next year Well I
lentísima tío el año que viene Bueno
think in fact next month no
creo que de hecho el mes que viene no el
next month or the next I have a
mes que viene o el otro tengo yo un
trial of the usual ones for a live show
juicio de Las de siempre por un directo
that I did with Mario in 2019 in
que hice con con Mario en el 2019 en el
2019 a live show that just as it ended
2019 un directo que tal y como terminó
okay or so it was the juno this that they did
vale o sea que eran los juno esto que
gue Okay when you do a
hacían gues Vale cuando tú haces un
guest on yuno it was different because it
guest en yuno era diferente porque no
wasn't like it was broadcast on my channel but it
era como que se emitía en mi canal sino
was a call from one channel to  another and it's
que era una llamada de un canal a otro y
actually a live stream from Marius
es en realidad es un directo de marius
on his channel they had to sue Marius
en su canal tenían que demandar a marius
but they're suing me okay but it's that
pero me demandan a mí vale e pero es que
apart or I mean I instantly deleted him
aparte o sea yo lo eliminé al instante
from my channel my channel you know that
de mi canal de mi canal de you know que
maybe had 100 150 viewers
a lo mejor tenía 100 150 espectadores
okay if anything okay and I deleted it I
vale si acaso vale y le lo eliminé le
apologized and he sued me for that which
pedí disculpas y me demanda por eso que
is an outrage what Marius said
es una barbaridad lo que dijo marius
but sue him now to me it's a kiss
peroo demándalo a él ahora mí es un beso
that anyway I wouldn't take
que de todas maneras yo no me tomaría en
anything Marius says seriously
serio cualquier cosa que diga marius
okay but m next year or
vale pero m el año o sea el mes que
next month I don't know if it's next month or the next
viene o el otro no sé si es el mes que
in two or three
viene o el otro dentro de dos o tres
months a trial for that which is like and it wouldn't
meses un juicio por eso que es como y no
work out better for you I say uh I mean I know that you're going to
te Salía mejor digo yo eh o sea que sé
have the headline on your face if they
que vas a tener el titular en faca si me
condemn me or whatever Okay but it wouldn't
condenan o lo que sea Vale pero no te
work out better for you to ask also he filed the lawsuit
Salía mejor pedir además puso la demanda
in 2023 in 2023 he filed the lawsuit
en el 2023 en el 2023 puso la demanda
which is how this is stated to you in
que es como a ti te afesta esto en el
2023 or so of course how not  they've had 4
2023 o sea claro como no han tenido 4
years not to sue because they put that
años no Para demandar pues mete esa
nonsense and it's like it didn't work out for you It was better than
tontería y es como no te Salía mejor que
talking to me that besides they can't even tell me
hablarme que aparte tampoco me puede
why if it's not even that I'm going to
para qué si es que ya lo ni siquiera
walk churra I want a little
saame de paseo churra Quiero un poquito
kiss a tirio kiss now I'll give you a for
beso un beso tirio ya te ya te doy un
you know that as if it's not even I
por sabes que como si es que ni siquiera
got to upload it to my YouTube channel
lo llegué a subir a mi canal de YouTube
never to you know as the
nunca al you know tal y como terminó la
call ended instantly I deleted it I
llamada al instante lo eliminé pedí
apologized for the guest what do you know I don't
disculpas por el invitado para qué sabes
know I don't understand much it's that I was going to
No sé no entiendo mucho es que te iba a
tell you it's not better to call me and such and such and
decir no te sale mejor llamarme y tal y
I'll delete it whatever but of course it
cual y yo lo borro lo que sea pero claro
's not even a thing that I
es que ni siquiera es una cosa que yo
but the foreras of gossiping
sino que la foreras de cotilleando
some of them okay by the way they have
alguna de ellas vale que por cierto
as a witness a forera who I hope doesn't
llevan de testigo una forera que espero
slip a single
que no se le escape ni un una sola
lie of those that my lawyer is going to ask her
mentira de las que le va a preguntar mi
because one single lie and I'm going
abogado porque una sola mentira y la voy
to put her in that in her day they didn't accept
a meter que en su día no me aceptaron
a complaint from me I'm going to put a false
una denuncia la voy a meter un falso
testimony of that you know that is like a
testimonio de eso saes que es como a una
forera they take Why do you take a
forera llevan Para qué llevas a una
forera if everyone knows that
forera si todo el mundo sabe que
publicly I boasted about  that you are friends
públicamente presumí de que sois amigas
and that she is a member of the forum that I reported,
y de que es una forera que yo denunci
you know. It seems that the member had the
sabes Se ve que la forera tenían el
video recorded, go know, how the hell
vídeo grabado vete to sab que cómo [__]
for that, that no one saw it to have
para eso que no lo vio nadie para tener
that recorded, you had to Record it in
grabado eso lo has tenido que Grabar en
the same live, whatever it takes to continue being
el mismo directo lo que sea para seguir
present in Javi's life, I think these are things
presente en la vida de Javi yo son cosas
that I don't understand, but of course you
que no lo entiendo pero que Claro tú
say Well, he put it there at the time but he
dices Bueno la puso en su momento pero
put it in 2023, he came to me with that
que la puso en 2023 me vino con esa
lawsuit, eh, which is like, and with this, what the
demanda eh que es como y con esto qué
[ __ ] do I do if this is erased, imo. Ah,
hago [__] hago si esto está borrs imo Ah
but well, the flera de cotill and they
pero bueno que la flera de cotill and lo
recorded it, they recovered it. But well, the
grabaron lo recuperaron Pero bueno yo el
issue of the lawsuit, man, I honestly feel
tema ese de demanda tío yo la verdad me
very lazy, I think they have to
da mucha pereza creo que que tienen que
be things. You know, very, very, very heavy,
ser cosas Sabes muy muy muy pesada muy
the one about lerl is a very heavy thing. Do
la de lerl es una cosa muy pesada hagan
what you have to do, the truth is
lo que tengan que hacer a mí la verdad
that it gives me quite a bit. The same thing, I think
que me da me da bastante Igual yo es que
there are certain ones that will mess it up, Marius. Eh,
hay determinadas te la Lio el marius Eh
yes, but I think you have to
sí pero que yo creo que tienes que
sue Marius, you understand, people
demandar a marius me entiendes personas
with whom it is not even worth
con las que ya ni ni me merece la pena
talking to me anymore and I'm not referring to  crypt Brook
hablar y no me refiero a crypt Brook
crypt Brook no, I don't have any
crypt Brook no le no le tengo ningún
kind of bad words for him, we send him our
tipo de de malas palabras le mandamos un
regards, but the cast is over, you see, they
saludo pero terminado elenco que ya ves
are people with whom you can't
que es gente con con la que no se puede
talk, there is no dialogue, there is nothing, if they
hablar no hay diálogo no hay nada si
simply have some guidelines from
simplemente tienen unas directrices de
someone, eh And they have to follow them
de alguien eh Y y tienen que cumplirlas
And then how are you not going to reason with
Y entonces como no vas a razonar con
those people because it is not possible, it
esas personas porque no se puede ya está
is like it is to frustrate me, I
sea en plan es como para frustrarme ya
already have that Stain on the table that I do not
ya tengo la Mancha esa en la mesa que no
understand very well, where did it come from that
entiendo muy bien De dónde ha salido que
you have guidelines to follow, as a
tien unas directrices a seguir di ser
colleague, you can easily do 10
colega puede hacer tranquilamente 10
days that I do not speak to Dallas, eh, I do not
días que yo no hable con el Dallas eh No
even know when the last time I spoke
sé ni cuándo fue la última vez que hablé
to him was, well, nothing, eh, I mean, not because we
con él No pues nada eh o sea no Porque
are fighting or anything like that,
estemos peleado ni nada por el estilo
but because it has not been, it is that you
sino porque no ha tado es que daros
realize that right now he is not involved in
cuenta que no está metido ahora mismo en
any controversy, I am now, but we
ninguna polémica yo estoy ahora pero
are each making some
estamos haciendo cada uno unos
content that we are not crossing paths, you
contenidos que no nos estamos cruzando
know. So not live, 4 other
sabes Entonces no en directo hace 4atro
days ago Yes, D told me something live. Ah
días Sí me dijo algo el D en directo Ah
well, no, it has not reached me, it has not reached me, it has
pues no lo no me ha llegado no me ha
not reached me, you know, but what
llegado no me ha llegado sabes pero que
guideline what if it is the truth I mean
directrice qué si es que es la verdad O
if the complaint does not exist and
sea si es que la denuncia no existe y
Cristo bru has stated that the complaint does not
Cristo bru ha puesto que la denuncia no
exist but if there are no more I don't
existe pero si es que no hay más No
understand why they get so angry, that is, I
entiendo por qué se pican tanto o sea
cry so much and so much I do not live off
tanto lloro y tanto tal no vivo del
gossip for my physical and mental health yes
salseo para mi salud física y mental sí
take care of your physical health I am definitely going to leave this
cuidado tu salud física voy a dejar
whole issue aside and
Definitivamente todo este tema de lado y
continue working on my thing which is
seguir trabajando en lo mío que son las
cryptocurrencies and trading especially
criptomonedas y el trading especialmente
now that we are in the middle of the Bull I have
ahora que estamos en pleno Bull he
taken a couple of actions and it is that I have
tomado un par de acciones y es que he
residential everything related to Dallas and
sidencial todo lo relacionado a Dallas y
pambi but if nobody talks about Dallas and
pambi pero si nadie habla de Dallas y
pambi now friend it's you eh you eh And
pambi ahora amigo eres tú eh tú eh Y
four Like you who are trying to
cuatro Como tú los que estáis intentando
revive the subject because you have had 2
revivir el tema porque habéis tenido 2
grams of attention but this I do not
gramos de atención pero esto yo ya no sé
even know how many times I have said it I am going to leave
ni Cuántas veces lo he dicho voy a dejar
the gossip about this subject since no that no I have
el salseo este tema ya que no que no
also stopped following the accounts
también he dejado de seguir las cuentas
related to the subject it is nothing
relacionadas con el tema no es nada
personal but I do it so as not to
personal pero lo hago para no volver a
fall again into the wheel of hate starting
caer en la rueda de odio a partir de
tomorrow I will only talk about cryptos and in
mañana solamente hablaré de criptos y de
fact I will not update the
hecho no voy a volver a actualizar la
collective complaint again I will continue working
denuncia colectiva Seguiré trabajando en
outside  of camera that there is no
fuera de cámara que no hay ninguna
complaint friend that there is no
denuncia amigo que no hay ninguna
complaint that there is not one that is a
denuncia que no la hay que eso es un
viral topic that you moved and because it had
tema viral que moviste y porque daba
many visits and and the topic is over Okay
muchas visitas y y se acabó el tema Ya
Javier Read it but with the photo on
alto Javier Léelo pero con la foto en
screen it gives it epicness that no man
pantalla le da epicidad que no hombre
that is sitting very well there is
que está muy bien sentadito ahí se está
contributing very well leave it there you know but
aportando muy bien déjalo ahí sabes pero
that is like blush a kiss that I do not know that
que es como colorete un beso que no le
that was a viral topic and he like in
que eso fue un tema viral y él como en
2017 the tip of liever the things that are
2017 la punta de liever la de cosas que
going to come out I do not know what And it was what
van a salir no sé qué Y fue lo que dije
I said in the summer Well now it has been fulfilled there was no
yo en verano Pues ahora se ha cumplido
restraining order nor was there a
ni había orden de alejamiento ni había
complaint from Ricky nor was there eh all the
denuncia de Ricky ni había eh todas las
things they said that there was about Dallas
cosas que dijeron que había de Dallas
with women with contracts with I do not know what
con mujeres con contratos con no sé qué
with I do not know how much With a contract yes there will be of
con no sé cuánto Con contrato si habrá
course that is not a secret but he does not
claro eso no es ningún secreto pero no
have the murky okay the
tiene la turbio vale la orden de
restraining order then Dallas stepped on Andorra and they
alejamiento luego Dallas pisó andorra y
started to say no that at 3
se pusieron a decir que no que a las 3
in the afternoon that no that no that it was a
de la tarde que no que no que era una
mob against Dalas that there was nothing there was no
turba contra Dalas que no había nada no
complaint nothing is going to happen to
había denuncia no le va a pasar nada al
Dala nothing is going to happen to him  with the Treasury
dala no le va a pasar nada con Hacienda
or rather nothing man nothing what I was saying if you
o sea nada tío nada lo que yo decía si
're here for me to talk about Pambi I
estás aquí para que hable de pambi te
recommend that you stop following me right now
recomiendo que dejes de seguirme ahora
since it won't happen again the
mismo ya que no volverá a pasar el
market is at a key point and
mercado está en un punto clave y
I need to be 100% focused on this I
necesito estar 100% focused en esto no
can't spend any more time fighting
puedo gastar más tiempo peleándome por
online with a criminal organization
internet con una organización criminal
or with people who don't want to be helped
ni con gente que no quiere ser ayudada
those who want to recover their money
los que quieren recuperar su dinero ya
are already moving the process the rest
están moviendo el proceso los demás solo
are only there to cause [ __ ] the
están para meter [__] el grupo
criminal group will be judged in due time
criminal será juzgado a su Debido tiempo
and really the rest of this is unnecessary said you
y realmente el resto sobra dicho esto ya
know don't fall for any more scams
sabéis no caigáis en ninguna estafa más
from these people or let them deceive you or
de esta gentusa ni que os engañen o
lie to you like people always do on the
mientan como siempre hacen la gente en
internet terribly evil no Christ
internet terriblemente mala no Cristo
bru Look I'm going to [ __ ] and I'm going to put
bru Mira voy a [__] y voy a meter
money into one of your copy trading come on
dinero en un copy trading tuyo vamos es
I don't know who the [ __ ] fell Senda a
que yo no sé quién [__] cayó Senda un
kiss because I wouldn't see you I mean come on
beso porque no te vería O sea pues vamos
I see you and you tell me to put your
yo te veo a ti y me dices que ponga tu
money into a copy trading of this type
dinero en un copy trading de este tipo
that you have to have desire that you have to
que hay que tener ganas que hay que
have desire for this let's go how long have we been
tener ganas de esto vamos cuánto tiempo
going I'm going to go I'm going to go
llevamos Me voy a ir voy me voy a ir
because I'm going to record  a video on the
porque voy a grabar un vídeo en el canal
main channel I was going to see some more things
principal iba a ver algunas cosillas más
but I'm leaving them for the morning because
pero las dejo para la mañana porque es
I'm going to record a video for the
que voy a grabar un vídeo para el canal
main channel handsome handsome and I want to record it
principal guapo guapo y quiero grabarlo
before going to bed I don't know if I
antes de irme a la cama No sé si he
put anything else in the title Oh about the
puesto algo más en el título Ah lo de la
community let's take a look that's
comunidad vamos a echar un vistazo es
true let's take a look at the
verdad vamos a echar un vistazo a la
community yes before we go come on guys let's
comunidad sí antes de irnos va cabrones
see I understand that the kids already
a ver entiendo que que los chavales ya
know that this exists it's not
sabéis que existe esto no está aquí
posted here okay just like you go to my
puesto vale tal y como entráis en mi
Twitter profile you can put it here
perfil de Twitter lo podéis poner aquí
okay you go in it's completely free and so
okay entráis es completamente gratuito y
on no but but it seems to me that it has been
demás no pero pero me parece que ha sido
the worst idea I've ever had in my [ __ ]
la peor idea que he tenido en la [__]
life because this is literally
vida porque es que esto es literalmente
bullying eh pop
bullying eh pop
[Music]
[Música]